Look like
That
Turn.
So, one more match. Uh, one more
exciting game. Gallagher United checking
up with team Aon.
Team A on one tossed to field first
at Gala United
after four balls two for no loss.
Arjun Sharma and Ketan Gura the opening
pair and Ankur Jane already started the
proceedings.
Oh that's very good bowling inside edge.
key.
Just a single.
Five balls only three runs conceded by
Ankor. Good start.
Very good over. Only three runs conceded
by Ankur Jane. One was gone. Three for
no loss. Gallagher. You write it.
Captain Rahul Panchel into the attack
starting with wide and single run five
for no loss 1.1.
Oh, that's a good strike. Straight
and four run. The fielder tried but that
will run away for four.
A clean strike as straight as an arrow
from Ketan.
Nine for no loss.
Once again, up and over over the
fielder.
They'll go for two runs
and two runs taken.
Fireworks something
to go. Chetan Guro.
He's playing well. And fireworks on the
sky.
Oh wow. once again high in the air and
this time taken
looking to connect for a big one but has
not got the proper elevation and good
cash at long gone
that's the first wicket fall of team
Gallagher United
Rahul Panchchal the captain strikes
1.4 4 11 41
That's gone miles in the air and well
taken. One more wicket in the name of
Rahul Panchchal the skipper.
Second wicket fall.
So back to back wickets. Two was gone.
11 for two.
Vikas Shiado the new batter
and the new starting Siddesh M
single taken by Arjun Sharma. Now Vikas
Yadu will face the first ball.
Swing and miss looking to play across
the line. Completely beaten. That's good
bowling from Siddesh Mo.
It's going down the leg side for wide by
by Mr. Singh.
Just tap and play and single tick.
15 for two.
only a single at long
So only five runs conceded by Siddesh
Muri. Very good bowling.
That's a good strike high in the AIR AND
OH
the fielder a bit of misjudgment
and went for four.
End of the over. Three gone. It's 20 for
two Gala United.
And that's taken. That's good catch at
mid wicket region. Third wicket fall and
Shashang strikes very first ball. 20 for
three.
He's
trying to spin towards going outside the
off line for wide
and well taken. Good catch.
We thought the ball will go up and over
of the covers fielder but no.
He was standing tall and well taken.
Good judgment. That's a one wicket fall
of Gala United. 23 for four.
Shashang strikes once again. Only three
runs conceded in four balls. He got two
wickets.
They're looking for two runs but uh
send back
Sanjay the new batter of the mark with
the single Arjun Sharma 907 with 14 on
strike last ball the fourth over
just guiding the ball towards that short
third man single to end of the over.
Very good over just five runs and two
wickets for Shashank.
Four gone 25 for four Gala I didn't
That's stumped out. Gone.
Good stumping from Rahul Panchchal
behind the stumps.
So one fall. Last ball coming up of the
first innings. 32 for5.
And that's end of the first inning. Five
was gone. 34 for five and 35 to win for
the team AON.
And we'll take a short break and come
back. Stay tuned to watch ICA Brokers.
ICS Lombard present Brokers Premier
League 2026 season 3.
Hello and welcome back once again. 35 to
chase for the team AON
and once again Mate Shawan Rahul
Panchchal.
Just one run conceded so far from Dendra
Kadu.
Wow, good bowling.
Leg by will be as leg by single by the
Empire.
Dendra has started really well. Only two
runs in the very first over.
One run only counted in his name.
Oh, this time losing the bit of
momentum. Dread for wide.
And this time being hammered for a big
one
that will run away for four runs.
Fulltos ball for the batter Rahul
Panchal the skipper. He hits fine for
boundary. One has gone seven for no loss
or charis run.
That's high in the air but safe. They're
going for two runs.
They'll get two runs.
So required and current run it is almost
same. Seven runs every over
important for the team is now to get a
wicket. And we're talking about the
wicket.
That's the wicket.
Gala United if they want to come back in
the match they need a two quick wickets
to break the momentum of Mites and Rahul
and Mit Johan departs
1.2941 2 941.
And this time up and over. Very well
played.
Excellent stop. But no, Sanjay try his
level best.
But that will go all the way for four
runs.
Excellent shot from Sidesh Mo. First
ball for four runs by 21 balls.
They're going for three.
Three runs taken.
19 runs in 20 balls.
multiple shot.
That's a universation from PY hit from
Caven Pedes
with the famous ad for the py head shot.
1.57 for one, 18 runs in 19 balls.
That's a good strike. We'll get only
single run.
No need to go for some big hitting
single single run. We'll be okay for the
team. Aon two gone. 18 for one.
That's gone high. India will land safe
between the fielders.
Only a single.
Siddesh Mor and R. Panchchala.
the two big destructive batters.
They can get easy runs, easy singles
and win this match. 16 runs, 17 balls
and this time keeper misses.
Well, that was a chance of catch.
The catch has been dropped. Single run
and clean bowl. Good bowling
or
displaying the STS and Wankadesh Chri
strikes.
It's an important breakthrough at their
very right point of time.
15 balls and 15 runs.
Mira Nike the new batter
fulls ball
going for two runs chance for the run
out and
the bowler didn't collect that ball
could be the chance for the big wicket
of Royal Panchchal
13 runs
in 14 balls.
A quick single taken.
13 balls and 12 runs.
And very easy flick from Rahul Panchchal
to take a single to end of the over.
Three gone 24 for two or
11 run 12 balls.
very crucial over the over of the match
coming up. 11 run
Here
we go.
Rahul Panchchal, the captain of team Aon
on strike.
Rogue
Noratch
win.
Je
single.
eight runs and 10 balls.
AK run.
in eight balls, three runs.
A run
short format game.
His
math
Chipped in the air. Still something to
cheer for the team. Gala United.
That's a one fall.
Check check check
hello check. Hello check. Okay,
two runs and six balls.
And the scores are level.
One run and five balls.
Ankur Jane the new batter on strike.
And with that single run
still there was chance something but
single run taken completed. That's a
victory for the team Aon. They won by
seven wickets
and the last match now coming up of
three overs. Match three winner versus
match four loser. So match for loser we
have the team galon.